<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:torrent="http://xmlns.ezrss.it/0.1/dtd/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>YayPonies - MLP:FIM 1080P iTunes Raw US</title>
    <link>/videos/rss/1it.rss</link>
    <description>Original iTunes US Ponies in 1080P.</description>
    <atom:link href="/videos/rss/1it.rss" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 12:57:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x17 - The End in Friend | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x17.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x17.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: The End in Friend; Season: 8; Episode: 17</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">http://yp1.yayponies.no/videos/torrents/YP-1R-08x17.mkv.torrent</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://yp1.yayponies.no/videos/torrents/YP-1R-08x17.mkv.torrent" length="72678" type="application/x-bittorrent"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <torrent:filename>YP-1R-08x17.mkv.torrent</torrent:filename>
      <torrent:contentlength>935898291</torrent:contentlength>
      <torrent:infohash>8C591944F51AC45D31E2FE74D215A79C9B7D80C4</torrent:infohash>
      <torrent:magneturi>magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8C591944F51AC45D31E2FE74D215A79C9B7D80C4</torrent:magneturi>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x16 - Friendship University | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x16-V2.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x16-V2.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Friendship University; Season: 8; Episode: 16</description> 
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>When Twilight learns that a new friendship school has opened in Las Pegasus, she and Rarity travel there to check it out. The school, Friendship University, is run by Flim and Flam and has enrolled Starswirl the Bearded, to Twilight's shock, and Chancellor Neighsay grants it full accreditation. Twilight and Rarity begin to investigate, with Rarity taking classes and Twilight sneaking into the brothers' office to search for evidence that the school is a fraud. They catch her in the act and threaten to publish a photo of the break-in to ruin her reputation; Twilight acquiesces at first in the face of Starswirl's disapproval, but Rarity persuades her not to give up. The two mares soon discover that the brothers are charging high fees for the worksheets needed to complete the coursework (based on a stolen copy of Twilight's own curriculum) and planning to use the money to expand their Las Pegasus resort. When Starswirl learns of the scheme, he intimidates them into refunding the students' money and shutting down Friendship University. He promises to attend the School of Friendship if he needs lessons in the future, but Twilight and Rarity are left wondering how Flim and Flam could have gotten the lesson plans.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x15 - The Hearth's Warming Club | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x15.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x15.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: The Hearth's Warming Club; Season: 8; Episode: 15</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>As the School of Friendship is about to go on winter break, a cloaked figure triggers a blast of purple goo that ruins its Hearth's Warming Eve decorations. Twilight Sparkle, Rainbow Dash, and Spike chase the figure into the students' dormitory but do not see it leave, leading them to conclude that one of these six is responsible. The guilty party will have to stay over the break for extra friendship lessons; if none of them confesses, all of them will stay and miss the holidays. As the students begin cleaning up and Rainbow calls them in for questioning, they describe the way their respective cultures celebrate the holidays. None of them confesses, leading to accusations and arguments that eventually spur Gallus to admit that he pulled the prank; he wanted to stay on campus with his friends instead of going home to Griffonstone and its dreary celebration. Having overheard, Twilight thanks him for his honesty but says that he must still face punishment. The other students volunteer to stay with Gallus, and Twilight invites the entire group to celebrate Hearth's Warming with her and her friends.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x14 - A Matter of Principals | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x14.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x14.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: A Matter of Principals; Season: 8; Episode: 14</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>The Mane 6 are called by the Cutie Map to a mission far away from Ponyville. Twilight leaves Starlight Glimmer to run the school and to do a scavenger hunt while they're gone. Discord appears and offers to help out, but Starlight refuses. A resentful Discord begins to unleash chaos on the school with Starlight trying to control each situation. She gets fed up with his antics, and banishes Discord from the school grounds with her magic. The scavenger hunt goes underway afterwards, but Discord, manifesting as a ghost, sabotages it. Starlight realizes what she did to Discord was wrong in turning down his offer to help, and apologizes to him. She unbanishes Discord and offers him the position of vice headmare. He accepts it and helps re-do the scavenger hunt. However, the Mane 6 return and Twilight reveals that Discord created a fake friendship mission to send them away, but thanks Starlight for helping run the school.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x13 - The Mean 6 | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x13.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x13.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: The Mean 6; Season: 8; Episode: 13</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Queen Chrysalis creates evil clones of Twilight and her friends to seize control of the Elements of Harmony and exact revenge against Starlight. Chrysalis and the clones search for the Elements in the Everfree Forest, where the real ponies and Starlight are on a camping trip. Wandering off from each other, the real ponies unknowingly encounter their clones, who mistreat and insult them before sneaking away. Mistaking the clones for their actual friends, the real ponies get into a heated argument when they eventually regroup. However, Twilight quickly manages to resolve the argument, and they happily resume their trip. Meanwhile, Chrysalis and the clones find the Tree of Harmony, but the clones are destroyed by the Elements when they attempt to use them to betray Chrysalis, who once again swears revenge against the oblivious ponies.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x12 - Marks for Effort | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x12.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x12.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Marks for Effort; Season: 8; Episode: 12</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Bored with their ordinary classes, the Cutie Mark Crusaders attempt to enroll at the more exciting School of Friendship, but Twilight turns them away, saying they have already mastered the curriculum. The Crusaders later meet a young student from the school named Cozy Glow, who is struggling with her homework, and figure that helping her would be just as good as attending Twilight's school. Cozy Glow aces her assignment under their tutelage, and asks them to help her prepare for an upcoming test. When Cozy Glow fails the test and explains the Crusaders' involvement, however, Twilight believes the Crusaders intentionally gave her poor guidance and bans them from the school grounds. Later, Cozy Glow confesses that she failed her test on purpose to make Twilight consider accepting the Crusaders as students like they wanted. After Cozy Glow apologizes to the Crusaders, Twilight withdraws their ban and gives them honorary diplomas, granting them positions at the school as official friendship tutors.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x11 - Molt Down | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x11.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x11.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Molt Down; Season: 8; Episode: 11</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Spike begins experiencing bizarre body changes such as breaking out in pimple-like blemishes, losing control of his fire breath, and emitting foul stenches. Smolder explains that Spike is molting, which all dragons undergo during adolescence; she adds that the molting process typically causes dragons to be kicked out of their homes, which Spike worries is the case when Twilight tells him to leave the Castle of Friendship to keep him from accidentally burning their belongings. When he visits Zecora for a solution, his smell unwittingly attracts a predatory roc that catches Zecora, as well as Rarity when she arrives for the zebra's remedies. Spike molts all of his skin to find he has grown a pair of wings, which allows him to fend the roc off and rescue his friends. Afterward, Twilight assures Spike that she has no intention of getting rid of him, and promises to help him get used to his changes.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x10 - The Break Up Break Down | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x10.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x10.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: The Break Up Break Down; Season: 8; Episode: 10</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>On Hearts and Hooves Day, Big McIntosh sends to Sugar Belle a romantic package that is lost in the mail, being sent to Sweetie Belle by mistake. When Big Mac notices Sugar Belle at Sugarcube Corner later, he overhears her talking with Mrs. Cake about ending a relationship with someone, and concludes that she means to break up with him. Spike and Discord attempt to console the heartbroken Big Mac, with Discord suggesting he assert himself by breaking up with her before she has the opportunity. After he does so, breaking her heart, Big Mac realizes he has only been letting out his frustrations and returns to her to have a proper conversation over their breakup. Sugar Belle reveals she never received Big Mac's package and had actually planned to end her business relationship with her cousin so she could begin working in Ponyville, never intending to leave Big Mac. Realizing their miscommunication, the two get back together.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x09 - Non-Compete Clause | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x09.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x09.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Non-Compete Clause; Season: 8; Episode: 09</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Applejack and Rainbow Dash compete with each other to receive the "Teacher of the Month" award at the School of Friendship. Twilight selects them to lead a field trip together to teach their students about teamwork, but their constant bickering over which activities they should do creates problems. Persuading Twilight to give them another chance, the two continue the trip by letting the other take the lead, which takes up more of their focus than teaching their students. When their polite argument over making a bridge leaves them stuck over a river, the students work together to save them. The students vouch for them as teacher of the month by telling Twilight that the two were arguing on purpose to teach them the incorrect way of working as a team, but Twilight catches on to the truth, causing Applejack and Rainbow Dash to argue all over again.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x08 - The Parent Map | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x08.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x08.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: The Parent Map; Season: 8; Episode: 08</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Starlight and Sunburst are unenthused to learn they have been summoned by the Cutie Map to their childhood home of Sire's Hollow, due to their strained relationship with their parents: Firelight, Starlight's over-affectionate father, and Stellar Flare, Sunburst's domineering mother. They are further dismayed when their mission appears to be settling a feud between the two parents, but find this is not the case after ending the fight quickly. Starlight and Sunburst try to avoid their parents as much as possible while they look for their real mission, only for their parents to continually meddle with their search. After finally snapping at their parents for their unwanted interference, Starlight and Sunburst realize their estrangement from them is the problem they were summoned to solve. The two complete their mission by apologizing to their parents, who agree to give them more independence.
</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x07 - Horse Play | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x07.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x07.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Horse Play; Season: 8; Episode: 07</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Twilight organizes a stage play honoring the anniversary of Princess Celestia's first raising of the sun. Learning that Celestia has never been in a play despite her love of theater, Twilight offers her the lead role, to Celestia's glee. As Rainbow Dash excitedly spreads the word of Celestia's involvement across Equestria, however, Twilight is mortified by Celestia's poor acting skills and fears that Celestia will humiliate herself in front of her subjects, but she keeps it to herself to avoid hurting Celestia's feelings. When the day of the play arrives and Celestia's performance has not improved, Twilight panics and unwittingly vents her frustrations with Celestia in front of her, causing Celestia to storm off. Twilight apologizes to Celestia for lying and admits she only intended to repay Celestia for her years of guidance. Celestia agrees to help Twilight salvage the play by directing the other actors from backstage, making it a success.</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x06 - Surf and/or Turf | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x06.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x06.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Surf and/or Turf; Season: 8; Episode: 06</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>The Cutie Map summons the Cutie Mark Crusaders to the hippogriffs' kingdom on Mount Aris, where half of its denizens have decided to live in the underwater city of Seaquestria as seaponies. Terramar, a young hippogriff whose parents live separately in each location, cannot decide whether he belongs on land with his father or underwater with his mother. The Crusaders are unable to agree among themselves—Sweetie Belle arguing for the mountain's captivating landscape while Scootaloo favors the fun of swimming with the sea creatures—which makes Terramar even more indecisive. The three arrange a gathering of hippogriffs and seaponies at the shoreline for Terramar, whose parents tell him he is not limited to choosing one place to live. Encouraged, Terramar settles on living as both a hippogriff and a seapony.</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x05 - Grannies Gone Wild | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x05.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x05.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Grannies Gone Wild; Season: 8; Episode: 05</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Rainbow Dash is eager to ride the Wild Blue Yonder, a famous roller coaster in Las Pegasus, before it permanently closes. Applejack agrees to take over Rainbow Dash's classes at the School of Friendship if she chaperones Granny Smith and her elderly friends for their annual Las Pegasus vacation, strictly instructing Rainbow Dash to never let them overexert themselves or leave her sight. Rainbow Dash reluctantly accepts, and attempts to convince the grannies to rest in their hotel so she can have time for herself. However, the grannies sneak off while Rainbow Dash discovers the coaster's long waiting line, forcing Rainbow Dash to spend most of the day following them and interfering with their exciting activities, much to their annoyance. When Rainbow Dash apologizes for ruining their fun and explains she is only following Applejack's instructions, the grannies laugh over Applejack's overprotectiveness and invite Rainbow Dash to ride the coaster with them, using their VIP passes to skip the line.</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x04 - Fake It 'Til You Make It | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x04.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x04.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: Fake It 'Til You Make It; Season: 8; Episode: 04</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Rarity leaves Fluttershy in charge of her boutique in Manehattan while she is out of town for a fashion show in Canterlot. Fluttershy is intimidated by the pushy customers, so Rarity advises her to wear an outfit to boost her confidence. Taking Rarity's advice to heart, Fluttershy begins dressing up and acting out different characters to match her customers' personalities, which helps the store's sales. However, she takes her role playing so far that she begins driving customers away with her rude behavior, getting rid of her raccoon helpers as well. The raccoons bring Fluttershy's friends to help, but she kicks them out of the store. Her friends then turn to Rarity, who fires Fluttershy, bringing her back to her senses. Fluttershy apologizes to her friends, and Rarity assures her that she already has the inner strength needed to succeed.</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x03 - The Maud Couple | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x03.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo//YP-1R-08x03.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: The Maud Couple; Season: 8; Episode: 03</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Pinkie Pie learns that her sister Maud is dating a stallion named Mudbriar, who has an interest in sticks similar to Maud's interest in rocks, and is as outwardly dull and blunt as she is. Although Maud and Mudbriar are happy together, Pinkie fails to notice their similarities, finding Mudbriar's personality and quirks to be annoying and strange. Unable to comprehend their relationship, Pinkie eventually becomes convinced that Maud prefers Mudbriar over her and flees to her family's rock farm in despair. After her sisters Limestone and Marble help Pinkie realize that Maud's happiness with Mudbriar is all that matters, Pinkie returns and makes peace with Mudbriar, putting up with him for Maud's sake.</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x02 - School Daze (2) | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x02.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo/YP-1R-08x02.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: School Daze (2); Season: 8; Episode: 02</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>A depressed Twilight mulls over her School of Friendship being unaccredited until Starlight Glimmer encourages her to try again, this time without following the EEA's rules. She and her friends attempt to convince the other species' leaders to let their students return to the school, only to learn that the students have all run away from home, unwilling to part with each other. The ponies discover that Sandbar has been hiding the other students at the Castle of the Two Sisters in the Everfree Forest, where they rescue them from being attacked by a horde of pukwudgies. The students agree to give the school another chance after the ponies assure them things will be different. Chancellor Neighsay confronts Twilight for her unauthorized re-opening of the school, but Twilight asserts her authority as Princess of Friendship and writes her own set of school rules to supersede those of the EEA. Twilight's friends use their own unique teaching methods to make the school more appealing, and the leaders allow their students to continue their studies in Equestria.</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic - 08x01 - School Daze (1) | 1080p.WEB-DL | YP-1R-08x01.mkv | YayPonies</title>
      <link>https://yp.coco-pommel.org/ypvideo/YP-1R-08x01.mkv</link>
      <description>Show Name: My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic; Episode Title: School Daze (1); Season: 8; Episode: 01</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <summary>Following their adventure to save Equestria from the Storm King (shown in My Little Pony: The Movie), Twilight Sparkle and her friends discover that the Cutie Map has expanded to cover lands beyond their kingdom. Twilight receives approval from the Equestria Education Association (EEA) to open a school devoted to teaching the benefits of friendship across these lands, with her friends serving as teachers and staff. She also welcomes five students from other species to attend: Gallus, a sarcastic griffon; Yona, a clumsy yak; Smolder, a cocky dragon; Ocellus, a timid changeling; and Silverstream, an excitable hippogriff. The students initially enjoy the school, but quickly grow bored as Twilight forces her friends to adhere to the EEA's strict guidelines for teaching. The five creatures decide to skip class along with their pony classmate, Sandbar, becoming fast friends. While playing, they accidentally wreak havoc on the school during an evaluation conducted by EEA head Chancellor Neighsay. Convinced that the non-pony students are dangerous, Neighsay immediately shuts the school down.</summary>
    </item>
      </channel>
</rss>
